老天  什么风把你吹来了
Goodness, what are you doing here?
我是收藏家  我收藏你宝贝女儿的作品
I collect. I collect your famous daughter.
能想办法给我个内部优惠价吗
If there's anything you can do to get me a family price.
还在那工作吗
You still where you used to be?
当然  我喜欢那里
Of course I am. I like it.
为什么要跳槽呢
Why would I change?
你呢  马克斯
And you, Max?
在国防部  从事国防采购吗
Defence. Defence procurement.
干这一行永远不会受罪
That's one business that's never going to suffer.
没有不景气的时候
Recession-proof.
这两天我还为我党
And these days I also raise a little money,
募集到了些资金
you know, for the party.
别对我说  我不关心政治
Don't look at me, I'm apolitical.
你什么都不关心吧  约翰尼
You're "A" Everything, aren't you, Johnny?
总有一天你得选择支持一边
You'll have to choose sides one day, you know.
记住  保持中立只有死路一条
Remember, you'll get killed in the middle of the road.